Guide to the University Archives Poster Collection, 1935-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
University Archives Poster collection 1935-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
44 linear feet Extent: 1,600 Items
The University Archives Poster Collection was compiled by University Archives staff from a variety of sources. The collection consists of approximately 1,600 posters, event calendars, programs and flyers publicizing various campus events, including movies, lectures, musical and theatrical performances, art exhibitions, and festivals. Dates of the posters range from 1935 to the present, but a majority of the posters range from 1970-1989.
UA.01.15.0011
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Provenance
The University Archives Photograph Collection received by the University Archives from a variety of sources.
Historical Note
The University Archives Poster Collection was compiled by University Archives staff from a variety of sources.
Collection Overview
The University Archives Poster Collection was compiled by University Archives staff from a variety of sources. The collection consists of approximately 1,600 posters, event calendars, programs and flyers publicizing various campus events, including movies, lectures, literary events, musical and theatrical performances (including Hoof 'N' Horn, Duke Players, and Duke Drama), concerts (including Duke ensemble groups and outside major attractions), art exhibitions, and festivals. Also included are basketball (men's and women's) team posters. Dates of the posters range from 1935 to the present, but a majority of the posters ranges from 1970-1989.
Subject Headings
Duke University; Duke University. University Archives; Posters; Posters -- Exhibitions
Related Material
Preliminary Inventory of the Hoof 'n' Horn Records, 1941 - 2006.
University Archives, Duke University.
Contents of Collection
- Container List
  - box 1 (Box 1)
  - The Hostage, (no year) October 11-14, 18-21 (Box 1)
  - Happy Birthday, Wanda June, (no year) April 7, 10, 14, 17 (Box 1)
  - Duke Players 1978-1979 Season (Box 1)
  - What the Butler Saw, (no year) April 17-20 (Box 1)
  - Noon and Children on their Birthdays, (no year) November 4-6 (Box 1)
  - Humpty Dumpty, (no year) December 3-4, 10-11 (Box 1)
  - The Public Eye, (no year) September 1-2, 7-8 (Box 1)
  - Chamber Music and This is the Rill Speaking, (no year) November 2-4 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Mound Builders, (no year) February 15-18, 22-25 (Box 1)
  - American Dream, (no year) September 2-4 (Box 1)
  - The Real Inspector Hound, (no year) September 2-3, 8-9 (Box 1)
  - Bent, (no year) April 13-16, 19-23 (Box 1)
  - Company Auditions, (no year) September 11-12 (Box 1)
  - Blithe Spirit, (no year) April 18-21 (Box 1)
  - How Could I Not Be Among You? and The What-Not, (no year) March 28-30 (Box 1)
  - The Next Generation and Switchboard: A Department Store Melodrama, (no year) March 28-30 (Box 1)
  - 5thof July, (no year) April 10-14, 17-21 (Box 1)
  - The Hotel Baltimore, (no year) October 2-5, 9-12 (Box 1)
  - Bad Habits, (no year) April 8-11, 15-18 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Spring Studio Theatre (Ways of Life and The Bishop of Mishigasi), 1977 March 18-20 (Box 1)
  - Marat Sade, 1977 February 10-13, 17-20 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - The Threepenny Opera, 1976 October 14-17, 22-24 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Folder Containing Newspaper Clippings, 1953-1960 (Box 1)
  - The Intellectual Ladies, (no year) February 23-25, March 2-4 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - The Corinthian, 1974 February 22-24 (Box 1)
  - The Glass Menagerie, 1949 November (undated-Thanksgiving) (Box 1)
  - The Little Foxes, (no year) December 2-5, 9-12 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Deathwatch, (no year) February 9-11 and (on opposite side) The Crucible (no year) December 3-5, 10-12 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - The Firebugs, (no year) October 20-23 and 27-30 (Box 1)
  - The Tempest, (no year) March 10-12 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Heartbreak House, (no year) April 30, May 1-2 and 7-9 (Box 1)
  - After the Fall, (no year) October 3-6, 10-13 (Box 1)
  - The Beeple, 1979 November 30, December 1-2 and 7-9 (Box 1)
  - JB, (no year) April 20-23 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire, 1973 November 30, December 1-2, 6-9 (Box 1)
  - Duke Players 1972-1973 Season (Box 1)
  - The Corinthian Program, 1974 February 22-24 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - The Corinthian Advertisement, 1974 February 22-24 (Box 1)
  - Blithe Spirit Auditions, 1974 March 18-19 (Box 1)
  - Type Cast and Water Spiders, 1973 April 6-8 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Duke University Moliere Festival, 1973 February 21-March 4 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - The Owl and the Pussycat, (no year) March 17-19 (Box 1)
  - The Author Made Me Do It and The Great American Cheese Sandwich, 1985 March 19-23 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Romeo and Juliet, 1986 February 14-15 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Hotel Baltimore, (no year) October 18-19, 24-27 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - “Studio Opera: An Opera Workshop Production of Scenes from La Serva Padrona, The Marriage of Figaro, Carmen, and La Boheme,” 1965 May 7-8 (Box 1)
  - The Hostage, undated (Box 1)
  - Summer Theater at Duke Auditions, 1973 April 24-25 (Box 1)
  - Equus, 1982 April 14-18, 20-24 (Box 1)
  - Theater Schedule, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Theater Schedule, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Twelfth Night, October 24-26, 30-31, November 1-2 (Box 1)
  - Bell, Book and Candle, (no year) October 28-31 (Box 1)
  - The Birthday Party, (no year) November 13-16, 20-23 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - The Hostage, (no year) October 11-14, 18-21 (Box 1)
  - The Firebugs, (no year) March 3-4 (Box 1)
  - The Public Eye, (no year) September 23 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, (no year) November 6-7 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Waiting for Godot, (no year) February 18-20 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Love’s Labour’s Lost, (no year) December 9-13 (Box 1)
  - Misalliance, 1982 February 24-27 (Box 1)
  - High Class Vaudeville, (no year) February 23-27 (Box 1)
  - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, (no year) November 30, December 1-3, 7-9 (Box 1)
  - Exposures, (no year) December 2-3, 6-10 (Box 1)
  - Carbonated Rainbow, (no year) December 3-6, 10-12 (Box 1)
  - Dark of the Moon, (no year) March 14-15 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - The Persecution…Marquis de Sade, 1969 October 30-31 and November 1-2 (Box 1)
  - The Hostage(September 7-8) and A Streetcar Named Desire (October 26-27) Open Auditions (Box 1)
  - Hedda Gabler, (no year) April 12-15, 19-22 (Box 1)
  - Jaques Brel is Alive and Well and Living in Paris Open Auditions, (no year) October 15-16 (Box 1)
  - Desire Under the Elms, (no year) March 8-9 (Box 1)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire, (no year) November 30, December 1-2, 6-9 (Box 1)
  - The Playboy of the Western World, (no year) December 8-11 (Box 1)
  - Clippings and Playbill, The Playboy of the Western World(1954), December 8-11 (Box 1)
  - The Infernal Machine, (no year) February 22-23 (Box 1)
  - Six Characters in Search of an Author, (no year) December 6-9 (Box 1)
  - Feiffer's People, (no year) August 30-31 (Box 1)
  - The Wind in the Willows Open Auditions, March 5-6 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Pirandello's Henry IV, (no year) March 5-6 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Finian's Rainbow Auditions, (no year) October 18-19 (Box 1)
  - The Imaginary Invalid, (no year) February 12-15, 19-22 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - The Madwoman of Chaillot, (no year) October 12-22 (Box 1)
  - Blood Wedding, (no year) April 20-23 (Box 1)
  - Finian's Rainbow (no year) December 8-12 (Box 1)
  - Henry IV Auditions, (no year) February 4-5 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - The Threepenny Opera Auditions, (no year) October 20 (Box 1)
  - The Intellectual Ladies Auditions, (no year) January 17-18 (Box 1)
  - A Long and Happy Life, (no year) July 9-11, 16-18 (Box 1)
  - American Dream, (no year) September 2-4 (Box 1)
  - Little Murders, Water Spiders and Type Cast Auditions, (no year) March 9-10 (Box 1)
  - The Bat, (no year) October 21-22 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - The Bald Soprano and The Maids, (no year) November 18-21 (Box 1)
  - The Imaginary Invalid Auditions, (no year) January 15-17 (Box 1)
  - Little Murders, (no year) April 19-22, 26-28 (Box 1)
  - Another Part of the Forest, (no year) November 10-13 (Box 1)
  - The Pleasure of his Company, (no year) October 25-26 (Box 1)
  - After the Fall Auditions, (no year) September 4-5 (Box 1)
  - Blood Relations, (no year) November 20-23 (Box 1)
  - The Tempest, (no year) February 28, March 1-2, 6-9 (Box 1)
  - The New Trial, (no year) November 19-22 (Box 1)
  - The Illusion, (no year) February 26-27, March 4-6 (Box 1)
  - Lysistrata, (no year) March 6-8 (Box 1)
  - Rhinoceros, (no year) October 15-17, 22-24 (Box 1)
  - Rashomon, (no year) October 17-19 (Box 1)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest, (no year) February 20-23 (Box 1)
  - Theatre of the Absurd Auditions, (no year) October 13-14 (Box 1)
  - A Thousand Clowns Auditions, (no year) September 27-28 (Box 1)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire Auditions, (no year) October 26-27 (Box 1)
  - A Night of One Act Plays: Pullman Car, Hiawatha, The Bear and Spreading the New, (no year) November 12-14 (Box 1)
  - Duke Arts Festival, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Twelfth Night, (no year) May 8-11 (Box 1)
  - White Lies, (no year) August 31-September 1 (Box 1)
  - The Lesson, (no year) September 1-3 (Box 1)
  - Marat Sade Auditions, (no year) January 13-15 (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Blithe Spirit, (no year) April 18-21 (Box 1)
  - Lady Julia and The Boor, (no year) April 8-12, 15-19 (Box 1)
  - Harvey Auditions, (no year) March 11-12 (Box 1)
  - Acts of Passion: A Festival of One-Acts and Recitals, (no year) February-April (Box 1)
  - General Meeting (October 12) and Another Part of the Forest Auditions (October 12-13) (Box 1)
  - The Winter's Tale reading, (no year) May 7-9 (Box 1)
  - The School for Scandal, (no year) March 11-12 (Box 1)
  - Harvey, (no year) April 21-23 (Box 1)
  - The Threepenny Opera, (no year) December 9-12 (Box 1)
  - To Kill a Mockingbird, (no year) April 9-13, 16-20 (Box 1)
  - The Good Woman of Setzuan, (no year) October 23-28 (Box 1)
  - Assorted Photographs from 1930s Productions (Box 1)
  - box 2 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Jazz Ensemble, March 23 (Box 2)
  - Duke Student Federalists, November 1 "Needed You to Help Build a Better Society", undated (Box 2)
  - Association of Duke Women present "Sirens," 1980 February 10 (Box 2)
  - "American Dreams," (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1981 February 5-15 (Box 2)
  - Mary Lou Williams, "Mary Lou’s Mass," 1978 February 25 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Union, "Star Trek comes to Duke," 1979 January 23 (Box 2)
  - La Boheme, 1979 December 10 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Research Conference "Women Men: Changing Roles" 1976 March 19 (Box 2)
  - Michael Best, Tenor, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Kathryn and Robin Huestis Piano Recital, 1975 April 6 (2 copies) (Box 2)
  - Hendrik VanderWerf on "Music and Musica in Learned Treatises of the Middle Ages and the Renaissance," 1975 April 3 (Box 2)
  - Susan Hirschmau Flute Recital, 1975 April 6 (Box 2)
  - Duke Collegium Musicum Presents "Bolognese School of Sacred Polyphony," 1975 April 8 (Box 2)
  - Karen vun Kannon (pianist), 1975 April 5 (Box 2)
  - Nancy Ferree Senior Organ Recital, 1975 April 6 (Box 2)
  - Pete Klausmeyer on "Electronic Music: Some Thoughts on Technique," 1975 March 29 (2 copies) (Box 2)
  - Patricia Goodson Junior Piano Recital, 1975 March 29 (Box 2)
  - Kate Ryan Piano Recital, 1975 March 28 (2 copies) (Box 2)
  - Robert Marshall on "Bach the Progressive: Some Thoughts on His Later Works," 1975 March 17 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Brass Quintet, 1975 March 21 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Wind Symphony Spring Concert, 1975 March 25 (Box 2)
  - "An Afternoon of New Music: Original Compositions of Lee Calhoun and Marty Herman," 1975 April 15 (Box 2)
  - A Concert of Baroque Chamber Music, 1975 November 3 (Box 2)
  - "Love Triangles in Opera" with Frances Redding and Wayne Lail, 1975 February 9 (Box 2)
  - The Merry Wives of Windsor (The National Opera Company), 1975 March 3 (2 copies) (Box 2)
  - The Durham Youth Symphony and the Orchestras of the Duke String School Spring Concert, 1975 April 19 (Box 2)
  - Tom Clark Organ Recital, 1975 April 20 (Box 2)
  - Composers Forum, 1975 April 22 (Box 2)
  - Giorgio Ciompi and Jane Hawkins Duo Recital, 1975 April 20 (Box 2)
  - Piano Recital (students of Loren Withers), 1975 April 27 (Box 2)
  - Michael Friedberg in "A Short Program of Guitar Music," 1975 April 23 (Box 2)
  - Quadrangle Pictures Schedule, Fall Semester, 1975 (Box 2)
  - A Song Recital by Steven Kimbrough and Ruth Friedberg, September 1975 20 (Box 2)
  - Duke Chorale with the Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1975 October 17 (Box 2)
  - A Guitar Recital by Francis Perry, 1975 October 9 (Box 2)
  - Walter Saul, 1975 April 25 (Box 2)
  - "A Performance of 20th Century American Vocal and Organ Music," by Weezie Knobloch, 1975 May 3 (Box 2)
  - Piano Recital (students of Ronald Fishbaugh), 1975 April 24 (Box 2)
  - A Piano Recital by Young Artists, 1975 May 31 (Box 2)
  - Robert Watkins Piano Recital, 1975 April 19 (Box 2)
  - Barbara Lister-Sink (pianist), 1975 November 31 (Box 2)
  - Mel Blank on "What’s Up, Duke?" 1975 April 15 (Box 2)
  - The Duke Collegium Musicum Presents "Acis and Galatea," 1975 November 9 (Box 2)
  - The Duke University Wind Symphony (November 18) and The Duke Jazz Ensemble (November 21), 1975 (Box 2)
  - William Mitchell (tenor) Junior Recital, 1975 December 7 (Box 2)
  - A Duo Recital with Alan and Diana Smith, 1975 November 23 (Box 2)
  - The Duke Symphony Orchestra Presents "The Sounds of America," 1975 December 10 (Box 2)
  - A Chamber Music Concert with Barbara Fecteau, Dorothy Gilmore, and Brian Chapman, 1975 December 16 (Box 2)
  - The Duke University String School Concert, 1975 December 14 (Box 2)
  - Intermission (A Chapel Hill Newspaper), 1975 September 21 (Box 2)
  - The Ciompi Quartet, 1975 March 1-2 (Box 2)
  - Francis Evans (harpsichord) Recital, 1975 February 16 (Box 2)
  - The Duke Symphony Orchestra, Duke University Chorale, and the Raleigh Civic Ballet Present "3 Original Ballets," 1975 February 7 (Box 2)
  - Guitar Lessons Advertisement, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Wind Symphony Lawn Concert, 1975 September 28 (Box 2)
  - The Clarion Wind Quintet American Music Project, 1975 October 20 (Box 2)
  - Sonata Recital with Arthur Benavie (violin) and Ruth Friedberg (piano), 1975 October 4 (Box 2)
  - A Duo Recital with Fred Raimi (cello) and Jane Hawkins (piano), 1975 October 18 (Box 2)
  - Fenner Douglas in a Lecture Recital on "The Organ Works of J.S. Bach," 1975 October 19 (Box 2)
  - The Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1975 October 24 (Box 2)
  - The Duke Jazz Ensemble and the UNC-G Jazz Band, 1975 October 21 (Box 2)
  - The Ciompi Quartet, 1975 November 1-2 (Box 2)
  - Intermission (A Chapel Hill Newspaper), 1975 March 30 (Box 2)
  - A Long and Happy Life (Summer Theater at Duke), 1975 July 9-11, 13, 16-18 (Box 2)
  - The Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1974 February 1 (Box 2)
  - Joe Easter Weekend, 1974 April 12-13 (Box 2)
  - Duke Artists Series, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
  - A Chamber Music Recital with Frances Evans (piano) and Hjourdis Tourian (violin), 1974 October 12 (Box 2)
  - Carl Patow (cello) Recital, November 19 and 23 (2 copies) (Box 2)
  - The Ciompi Quartet, 1974 October 26 (Box 2)
  - The North Carolina Symphony Woodwind Quintet, 1974 November 2 (Box 2)
  - The Collegium Musicum Presents "A Petrarch Concert," 1974 October 29 (Box 2)
  - "A Program of Songs by Robert Burns" by James T. Cleland (reader), John Hanks (tenor), and Ruth Friedberg (piano), 1974 October 27 (Box 2)
  - The Duke Wind Symphony Kioz (or Kidz) Konzert, 1974 December 5 (Box 2)
  - John Hanks and Ruth Friedberg Present "American Art Songs," 1974 November 20 (Box 2)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 1974 November 15 (Box 2)
  - Where Has Tommy Flowers Gone? (Summer Theater at Duke), 1974 July 12-14, 19-21 (2 copies) (Box 2)
  - Triangle Symphony Orchestra Presents "Summer Serenade," 1974 June 2 (Box 2)
  - "An Evening With Iain Hamilton," 1974 December 2 (Box 2)
  - Mary Margaret Samson Piano Recital, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Duke Collegium Musicum Presents "Music During the Schism: French Sacred and Secular Music of the Late XIVth Century," 1974 December 10 (Box 2)
  - Stephen Kort Faculty Recital (piano), 1974 December 14 (Box 2)
  - Sinfonia, 1974 July 26 (Box 2)
  - Rene Saorgin (organ), 1974 February 3 (Box 2)
  - The Duke University Chorale Presents "King David," (undated) (Box 2)
  - The Duke University Wind Symphony Spring Concert, 1974 March 19 (Box 2)
  - Durham Civic Choral Society, 1974 March 31 (Box 2)
  - The Duke University Chorale On Tour, 1974 March 8-17, 21 (Box 2)
  - The Duke University Chorale, 1974 March 21 (Box 2)
  - The Colonel and Mrs. Van R. White Oriental Art Collection, 1974 March 3 (Box 2)
  - Duke Summer Theater Advertisement, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Mattiwilda Dobbs (soprano), 1974 November 5 (Box 2)
  - David J. Hurd, Jr. Organ Recital, 1974 August 4 (Box 2)
  - The Durham Youth Symphony and the Orchestras of the Duke String School, 1974 December 15 (Box 2)
  - Jewish-Christian Dialogue on "Human Rights," 1974 March 3 (Box 2)
  - "The Wood Engravings of Winslow Homer" Exhibition, 1974 March 31 (Box 2)
  - Marian McPartland and her Trio, 1974 April 21 (Box 2)
  - The North Carolina Symphony Woodwind Quintet, 1974 May 4 (Box 2)
  - William F. Buckley on "Some of the Problems of Freedom," 1974 December 5 (Box 2)
  - Ritha Devi, 1974 March 23 (Box 2)
  - The Ciompi Quartet, 1974 March 30 (Box 2)
  - Broadway at Duke, Grease, 1974 February 15 (Box 2)
  - Duke Union Major Attractions, The Greg Allman Tour, 1974 March 17 (Box 2)
  - Duke Dance Group in Concert, 1974 February 8 (Box 2)
  - Freewater Films Presents The Other, 1973 September 14 (Box 2)
  - Freewater Films, 1973 Schedule (Box 2)
  - Freewater Films Presents Erich von Stroheim’s Greed, 1973 September 20 (Box 2)
  - Freewater Films Presents Akiro Kurosawa’s Rashomon, 1973 November 8 (Box 2)
  - Freewater Films Presents The Lady Vanishes, 1973 October 4 (Box 2)
  - Freewater Films Presents The Adventurer, The Navigator, and "A Short History of Animation: The Cartoon 1879-1933", 1973 (Box 2)
  - The Chamber Dance Group, 1973 March 30 (Box 2)
  - The National Opera Company Roster, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - The Yeomen of the Guard (The Durham Savoyards), 1973 May 18-20, 25-26 (Box 2)
  - Duke Dance Group Dance Festival, 1973 February 21-24 (Box 2)
  - Inauguration of Conscience, 1973 January 18, 20-21 (Box 2)
  - Martha (The National Opera Company), 1973 May 14 (2 copies) (Box 2)
  - Ramsey Clark on "Crime in America—1973," 1973 April 19 (Box 2)
  - The Blackburn Literary Festival Presents Anthony Burgess, 1973 April 17 (Box 2)
  - Applause,1973 January 21 (Box 2)
  - Two Gentlemen of Verona, 1973 October 17 (Box 2)
  - Sander Vanocur on "The First Amendment and the Media," 1973 February 13 (Box 2)
  - Cosi Fan Tutte (Canadian Opera Co.), 1973 February 12 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Letter, 1973 April 4 (Box 2)
  - Sinfonia a V, 1973 July 31 (Box 2)
  - George Baylin on "The Roll of X-Ray in Medical Care,"1973 November 8 (Box 2)
  - The Nutcracker(NCSA School of Dance), 1973 December 12 (Box 2)
  - Italian Tour Itinerary, 1973 June 18 (Box 2)
  - Merton of the Movies (Summer Theater at Duke), 1973 June 1-3 (Box 2)
  - The Collegium Musicum Presents "Music From the Court of Henry VIII," 1973 December 11 (Box 2)
  - The Duke Chamber Orchestra, 1973 November 18 (Box 2)
  - Carlos Montoya (program), 1973 October 24 (Box 2)
  - Ronald Fishbaugh Faculty Recital, 1973 November 2 (Box 2)
  - Stewart Udall on "Energy, Environment, and the Remaking of Tomorrow," 1973 October 22 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Moliere Festival, 1973 February 21-March 4 (Box 2)
  - Benny Goodman, The Charismatic King of the Swing Era, Homecoming, 1973 October 13 (Box 2)
  - Freewater Thursday: A History of the Cinema, 1973 September–December (Box 2)
  - You’re a Good Man, Charlie Brown (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1972 December 1-3, 9-10 (Box 2)
  - B.F. Skinner, 1972 October 26 (Box 2)
  - Emporer Delle Ojo and His Cultural Group, 1972 November 3 (Box 2)
  - Robert Rosenblum on "Abstract Expressionism and the Northern Romantic Tradition," 1972 November 27 (Box 2)
  - Original Prints, 1972 October 4 (Box 2)
  - Recent Tapestries by Silvia Heyden, 1972 March 11 (Box 2)
  - John Hallowell on "Democratic Theory: Principles and Prospects," 1972 September 26 (Box 2)
  - Murray Perahia (pianist) Publicity Pamphlet, 1972 (Box 2)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre, 1972 December 8 (Box 2)
  - Christopher Parkening, 1972 November 28 (Box 2)
  - Museum Without Walls: A Series of New Films on Art, 1972 September 17, 24, October 1, 8, 15 (Box 2)
  - Hair, 1971 November 15-18 (Box 2)
  - Nicolai Gedda (tenor) Recital Program, (undated) (2 copies) (Box 2)
  - Jewish Arts Festival, 1971 April 3-6, 8-12 (Box 2)
  - Theodore W. Schultz on "Notes on China," 1971 February 17 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Department of Music Musical Events Calendar, 1971 (Box 2)
  - New Performing Dance Company Program, (undated) (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Flyer/Insert(?) on Hands Across the Water: The British-American Heritage Quilt, 1971 (Box 2)
  - James Merrill Poetry Reading, 1971 October 10 (Box 2)
  - Vladimir Ashkenazy Publicity Flyer, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Margaret Atwood, 1971 April 23 (Box 2)
  - Quadflix, Fall Semester Schedule, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Humor Extravaganza, 1971 April 14-15 (Box 2)
  - British Airways, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Khoo Pu Nin and Melissa L. Yoder Senior Art Exhibition, 1971 March 17-April 5 (Box 2)
  - Look Back in Anger (Summer Theater at Duke), 1971 June 17-19, 24-26 (Box 2)
  - The Decline and Fall of the World As Seen Through the Eyes of Cole Porter(Summer Theater at Duke), 1971 June 25-26, July 1-2 (Box 2)
  - Suk Trio, 1971 October 22 (Box 2)
  - North Carolina Chamber Players, 1971 November 19 (Box 2)
  - Alban Berg Quartet, 1971 March 4 (Box 2)
  - Student Week, 1971 April 5-10 (Box 2)
  - Lucille Cole Exhibition, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Quadrangle Pictures Presents The African Queen, 1971 June 27 (Box 2)
  - The Concert Band, 1971 November 5 (Box 2)
  - Black Light Theatre of Prague, 1971 October 5 (2 copies) (Box 2)
  - "From Slave to Siren: The Victorian Woman and her Jewelry" Exhibition, 1971 May 9-June 7 (Box 2)
  - The Duke University Department of Music Presents a Chamber Music Concert, 1965 March 10 (Box 2)
  - Book Collector’s Contest, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Promises Promises (Hoof 'N' Horn), April 5-6 (Box 2)
  - The Shakespeare Playhouse Presents Twelfth Night (May 15), The Taming of the Shrew (May 16), Hamlet (May 16) (Box 2)
  - Springfest (undated) (Box 2)
  - Jackson Browne with Batdorf and Rodney, September 22 (Box 2)
  - Duke Arts Festival: "Interface," 1970 February-March (Box 2)
  - The Nutcracker, 1970 December 16 (Box 2)
  - Barbara Sydenham Thompson Exhibition, 1970 November 22-December 18 (Box 2)
  - Loren Withers Beethoven Recital, 1970 December 12 (Box 2)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1970 April 14 (Box 2)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre, 1970 April 17 (Box 2)
  - Unidentified Schedule, Fall 1970 (Box 2)
  - Synergic Acoustical/Visual Systems, 1970 April 3-5 (Box 2)
  - box 3 (Box 3)
  - "A Festival of Polish Music," November 7 and 11 (Box 3)
  - Jacob Lateiner (Box 3)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, Summer (Box 3)
  - East Campus Swim-A-Thon (Box 3)
  - Anything Goes Program (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1986 April 4-5, 10-12 and May 2-3 (Box 3)
  - Anything Goes (Hoof 'N' Horn), 1986 April 4-5, 10-12 and May 2-3 (Box 3)
  - Duke's Annual Employee Day and Family Carnival, 1985 May 11 (Box 3)
  - Duke University Chorale, 1985 March 15 (Box 3)